My name is Gloria. I work at uh Manual
Life as a long-term disability manager
in Montreal. The best part of working
directly with the customers is that you
see the process and you see the success
stories. So when someone is successful
with the fact that we helped throughout
the whole process and they get to that
point of a successful return to work,
that's by far the best part. There's
some people who go through really rough
times and if you can assist them with
finding the right medical professional
and it unlocks a whole different
treatment care for them. It really
benefits them in the right in the long
term. There are boundless opportunities
here. Myself, I went through short-term
to long-term disability. I have
colleagues who went from disability to
um sales teams having a bit of a medical
background to better understand what
people are going through. If you have a
passion, I think for people, I think
it's a it's a fit cuz those are things
that you can learn with time. Our
manager always tells us, listen, if you
see something that you might that might
peique your interest, let me know. Uh we
have a great team. There's always
someone who's ready to help.